Efe Toker

Istanbul, Istanbul, Turkey



efetoker@gmail.com



05352748316



linkedin.com/in/efetoker

Summary

Hi, I am a Frontend Web Developer with 5 years of freelance and 4 year full-time working experience. I have a fast learning and willing personality in my work. I have an experience scale from Angular 10+ to React Native or PHP. I'm also extremely rigorous and perfectionist in my code, exactly as an User-Interface Developer should be!

Experience



Frontend Team Lead

MTM Medya Takip Merkezi Apr 2018 - Present (3 years 9 months +)

Senior Frontend Developer

MTM Medya Takip Merkezi Jul 2017 - Present (4 years 6 months +)

Software Development Intern

IMMIB - Istanbul Minerals and Metals Exporters Association Sep 2014 - Jun 2015 (10 months)

Education

Anadolu University

Lisans, Management Information Systems 2017 - 2019

Istanbul Kultur University

Önlisans, Computer Programming 2015 - 2017

Bahcelievler Sehit Osman Yildiz M. T. A. L.

Lise, Web Programming 2011 - 2015

Skills

Angular 9 • OOP (Nesne Yönelimli Programlama) • Kullanıcı Deneyimi • Web Development • Ön Uç Geliştirme • Yazılım Geliştirme • Web Projesi Yönetimi • Web İçeriği • Metin Yazarlığı • Arama Motoru Optimizasyonu (SEO)